(Penny:)You know, not an attractive
quality in a woman, Leonard.
(Penny:)Not judging,
just my opinion.
(Leonard:)Well, The point is,
if this got out,
(Leonard:)it would destroy Howard
and Raj's friendship.
(Penny:)You don't have to worry.
(Penny:)Unlike Amy and Priya,
I know how to keep a secret.
(Leonard:)You're the one who told Amy
in the first place.
(Penny:)In confidence!
(Raj:)Hello, Mummy. Hello, Daddy.
How are you?
(Mrs Koothrappali(on webcam):)We're very rich
in a very poor country.
(Mrs Koothrappali(on webcam):)So, all in all,
can't complain.
(Dr Koothrappali:)So, Priya,
(Dr Koothrappali:)how are enjoying
staying with your brother?
(Priya:)It's fine. But if
I'm going to stay
(Priya:)in Los Angeles much longer,
(Priya:)I think I should
get my own place.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Why?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Is Rajesh not making you
feel comfortable?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Rajesh, why aren't you making
your sister comfortable?
(Raj:)I am making her comfortable.
(Raj:)Besides, she's not
sleeping here
(Raj:)half the time anyw...
(Sheldon:)What?
(Dr Koothrappali:)Where are you
sleeping, Priya?
(Priya:)It's a figure of
speech, Daddy.